(Sheldon:)- It was a drizzly Tuesday.
- Okay.
(Penny:)You promised me
you would keep my secret...
...so you are just gonna have to
figure out a way to do it.
(Sheldon(entering):)Leonard, I'm moving out.
(Leonard:)What do you mean
you're moving out? Why?
(Sheldon:)There doesn't have to be a reason.
- Yeah, there kind of does.
- Not necessarily.
(Sheldon:)This is a classic example
of Münchausen's trilemma.
(Sheldon:)Either the reason is predicated on a series
of sub-reasons leading to regression...
...or it tracks back to axiomatic statements,
or it's ultimately circular...
...i. e., I'm moving out
because I'm moving out.
(Leonard:)I'm still confused.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I don't see
how I could've made it any simpler.
Hey, qu'est-ce que c'up?
(Raj:)We just got back from that exhibit
of those plasticized cadavers.
(Howard:)Some of those skinless chicks were hot.
(Sheldon:)If you'll excuse me, I'm going to pack.